Beware the witch.
The Beldham is a horror film directed by Angela Gulner.
At the edge of postpartum psychosis, new mother Harper moves in with
her own mother at their family's rural farmhouse.
Soon she finds herself hunted by a threatening
monster who has designs on her child.
Sadie, played by Patricia Heaton.
Harper, played by Katie Parker.
Bette, played by Emma Fitzpatrick.
Carol, played by Angela Baumgardner.
Lois, played by Sabreena Iman.
The Beldham (also known as The House at Hallow End) is a 2024 American psychological
horror film written and directed by Angela Gulner in her directorial debut.
The film stars Patricia Heaton, Katie Parker, Emma
Fitzpatrick and Corbin Bernsen.
It follows a young mother with a child returning to her mother's family
home, where something evil threatens her and her child.
Signature Entertainment released the film on video on demand in the United
Kingdom, Ireland and Latin America on October 20, 2025 .
The film was released by Quiver Distribution in the
United States on November 7, 2025.
The tone is dark.